Ivan Shtyfurko

Frontend developer

wanzikhn@gmail.com

Vinnytsia

@vangen32



Summary

For the past 4 years of commercial experience I have been mostly responsible for the frontend part.

I am proficient in C# , utilizing Unity and Windows forms or WPF for mobile/desktop applications. I have been developing a mobile game and created desktop UI's for management purposes. I also have experience with .Net Framework.

I have strong experience with HTML, CSS, TailwindCSS, JS ,TS , Vue 3, creating admin panel UI's and online gaming websites, but also familiar with other popular frontend frameworks.

Have experience both working remotely and in-office.

Professional Skills

HTML, CSS, JS, TS, Vue3 (VueRouter, Pinia, Vuex), Tailwind, EJS C#, .Net Framework

NestJs, Asp.Net Core, Docker, Nginx

Work experience

Freelance

A few major projects I can mention are:

01/2022 - present

- 1) A project for a non-profit organization, which involved building an interactive map website. I have integrated a map and worked with multiple map providers and geocoding services as well as created most of the UI.
- 2) A frontend for a CRM system for an agroculture company. This gave me a great experience in creating graphs and charts. Written in Vue3, utilizing the best and recent practices and libraries.

Sincos Development

Middle frontend developer 09/2023 - 04/2024

I was responsible for creating a website for a gaming platform. It was written in Vue3 utilizing Socket.io. I was creating both socket and HTTP clients, stores and components with complex animations. As well as that I have managed a small frontend team, so I was directly involved in the project's architecture and planning.

Sincos Development

C# developer 11/2019 - 10/2023 Firstly, I was creating desktop admin panels, using Windows Forms. I have build the whole app from scratch and after upgraded it to WPF instead, preserving all of the business logic.

Then, I have switched to Unity 3D development, and was involved in building a gaming app for mobile platforms. I have worked with assets, bundling and created whole scenes and scripts for the game.

Education -

Vinnytsia Institute of Trade and Economics of State University of Trade and Economics

2014 - 2019

Master's degree in Organizational Trade Management